http://www.rotowire.com/privacy.php

Here at Roto Sports, Inc. (“RotoWire”, “we”, “us”, “our”), we are committed to you and to protecting your privacy rights. The information we collect about you is used to provide you with a more personalized and richer experience while visiting our network of websites, including RotoWire.com and Rotosportsinc.com.
RotoWire.com does not sell the email addresses of its users to third parties.
As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to inform our members, visitors, and the parents of children using or visiting the Roto Sports, Inc. Network how we use and protect the information that we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy statement.
WHAT INFORMATION DOES ROTOWIRE COLLECT?
Personal Information
You may visit and use many features on the Roto Sports, Inc. Network without completing any registration at all. However, in order to purchase products, complete surveys, enter contests and sweepstakes, participate in polls, online chats and forums, or enter other enhanced, member areas of the Roto Sports, Inc. Network, we may require you to provide us with certain contact and/or demographic information and/or to become a registered member of certain divisions of the Roto Sports, Inc. Network. When you become a registered member, we require you to provide us with your contact information (including your name and email address) and date of birth, as well as to create a password. As our goal is to make your experience as easy and enjoyable as possible throughout the entire Roto Sports, Inc. Network, this contact information is shared among the various divisions of the Roto Sports, Inc. Network, although at this time separate registration may be necessary.
Location Information
Users are typically asked to provide their state of residence, which allows us to send targeted offers for DFS (Daily Fantasy Sports) and sports betting based on the legality of these services in a given state. If a user wishes to purchase a NFL or MLB magazine, they will also be asked to provide a valid address for the magazine to ship to. This information is stored in our database for subscribers who wish to purchase a magazine in the future, but anyone that wishes we delete this information can contact support@rotowire.com.
League Information
Some benefits offered on RotoWire.com rely on customization of tools and information based on your fantasy sports league(s) and respective team(s). In order to improve applicability of the tools and information you see, we ask you to provide us with access to import those leagues, typically by logging in to your league host or explicitly granting permission for our tools to access your data. We do not store your login information on our servers, as we either get permission from you to access the league via an API or rely on the cookies of your league host to grant access. We may also collect crash data to help in the diagnosis of failed imports via the My Leagues feature. The disclosure of this information is entirely optional and not required in order to have a RotoWire account or subscription.
Furthermore, when a draft file -- which includes, but is not limited to, information regarding league name, team names, scoring settings, roster settings, draft picks, keepers, rankings modifications and projections modifications -- is exported to our servers from one of our devices, we log the date/time of export, device type (PC software, OSX software, iPhone, iPad) and sport. This allows our support team to view a user’s draft setup and assist in troubleshooting for many of these products. Like league data, the disclosure of draft information is entirely optional and not required in order to have a RotoWire account or subscription.
Credit Card Information
If you purchase a subscription to RotoWire.com or any products on the website, you will additionally need to provide us with your credit card and shipping information, or you have the option to send us a check. Any payment information is not stored directly on RotoWire.com, but rather by our secure, third-party payment processing partners PayPal (or its subsidiary Braintree.com). The PayPal privacy policy can be found here, while the Braintree privacy policy is found here.
Electronic Identification Data
We process the IP address of the device you log in with in order to enable communication between your device and our server; to determine your approximate geolocation which may be further used for service customization (for instance to provide appropriate content for your language of choice and gambling-related content that is legal in your jurisdiction) as well as for analytical purposes. More about how we process your data for analytical purposes you may find in our Cookie Policy (see below).
The processing of details about the browser and operating system you use is necessary to ensure the regular provision of our services to you. Also, sometimes we will need this data to solve some technical problems if they emerge.
Internet Cookies
You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognise repeat site visits and as an example, re-call your name if this has been previously supplied. We may use this to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Site, target the advertising and assess general effectiveness of such advertising.
Cookies do not attach to your system and damage your files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature.
However, a full subscription to RotoWire.com requires that your browser enable cookies or your access to the site likely won't work.
In addition, some of the third-party advertisers and ad networks we run on our sites use cookies. Information on how to opt out of those cookies is below.
HOW DOES ROTO SPORTS, INC. USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?
E-mail Notification
We may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about new services on the Roto Sports, Inc. Network, special offers we think you'll find valuable and important functionality changes to the web site. If you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other information request or distribution, simply submit such a request to us at support@rotowire.com. Members may also receive electronic newsletters from one or more divisions of the Roto Sports, Inc. Network. If you would rather not receive any of these newsletters, you may click on the link at the end of the newsletter, or notify us at support@rotowire.com.
RotoWire.com does not sell the email addresses of its users to third parties.
Disclosure to Third Parties
Subject to your express opt-in approval, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties, including e-commerce partners, who assist Roto Sports, Inc. by providing services to users of the Roto Sports, Inc. Network. We also may share your personally identifiable information at any time if compelled to do so in order to comply with any applicable law or valid legal process.
Should you change your mind about the information you've provided to us or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal information you gave us. You can do this simply by contacting us in any of the simple ways set forth below in the section entitled " How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?"
HOW DO WE PROTECT CUSTOMER INFORMATION?
We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. Member personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems.
To ensure compliance with updated security technology, we recommend using one of the following browsers, each of which can be downloaded free of charge: Google Chrome (https://www.google.com/chrome/), Mozilla Firefox (http://www.firefox.com) or Safari (https://www.apple.com/safari/). To ensure the highest level of security available today, we suggest that you choose the 128-bit encryption version from the download options. If you do not have access to a browser that supports at least 48-bit encryption, your information may not be processed by our servers, or may not be securely transferred through your web browser to our servers.
Unfortunately, when you submit information to us (or to any other website) over the Internet, the information may travel over many networks and systems that are not under our control and, during such time, can be intercepted. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Roto Sports, Inc. can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Further, anything you voluntarily provide in any public area of the Internet, including on the Roto Sports, Inc. Network, will be publicly available to other visitors on that web site and potentially to other third parties, and you should always exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose any of your personal information.
DATA CONTROLLER AND DATA SUBJECTS
By using RotoWire services you may disclose various pieces of information, including those that would be considered personal data. When your personal data is processed then you are considered a data subject and you are entitled to exercise your rights that are explained in this Privacy Policy. Taking into account that we determine the purposes and means of processing personal data on RotoWire we are legally considered as data controller over your personal data on this website. Being a data controller provides us the opportunity to process your personal data, but also obliges us to protect them.
HOW DO YOU OPT OUT? HOW DO YOU CHANGE THE INFORMATION WE HAVE FOR YOU?
We give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from the Roto Sports, Inc. Network. To request that your information be removed from our database or that certain information previously provided to us be updated or modified, or that we not send you any future communications, simply contact us in any of the following manners:
Send an e-mail to: support@rotowire.com
Send a letter to:
Roto Sports, Inc.
Attn: Customer Service
740 Regent St. Suite #200
Madison, WI 53715
SHORT CODE TERMS
When you opt-in to the Service, we will send you an SMS message to confirm your signup.
You can cancel the SMS service at any time. Just text "STOP" to 27526, after you send the SMS message "STOP" to us, we will send you an SMS message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive SMS messages from us. If you want to join again, just sign up as you did the first time and we will start sending SMS messages to you again.
If at any time you forget what keywords are supported, just text "HELP" to 27526. After you send the SMS message "HELP" to us, we will respond with instructions on how to use our service as well as how to unsubscribe.
We are able to deliver messages to the following mobile phone carriers:
Major carriers: AT&T, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, T-Mobile, U.S. Cellular, Alltel, Boost Mobile, Nextel, and Virgin Mobile. Minor carriers: Alaska Communications Systems (ACS), Appalachian Wireless (EKN), Bluegrass Cellular, Cellular One of East Central IL (ECIT), Cellular One of Northeast Pennsylvania, Cincinnati Bell Wireless, Cricket, Coral Wireless (Mobi PCS), COX, Cross, Element Mobile (Flat Wireless), Epic Touch (Elkhart Telephone), GCI, Golden State, Hawkeye (Chat Mobility), Hawkeye (NW Missouri), Illinois Valley Cellular, Inland Cellular, iWireless (Iowa Wireless), Keystone Wireless (Immix Wireless/PC Man), Mosaic (Consolidated or CTC Telecom), Nex-Tech Wireless, NTelos, Panhandle Communications, Pioneer, Plateau (Texas RSA 3 Ltd), Revol, RINA, Simmetry (TMP Corporation), Thumb Cellular, Union Wireless, United Wireless, Viaero Wireless, and West Central (WCC or 5 Star Wireless).
As always, message and data rates may apply for any messages sent to you from us and to us from you. You will receive 1 msg/req. If you have any questions about your text plan or data plan, it is best to contact your wireless provider. For all questions about the services provided by this short code, you can send an email to support@rotowire.com.com or (888) 201-3057.
If you have any questions regarding privacy, please read our privacy policy.
THIRD-PARTY BANNER ADVERTISING OPT OUT
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.
You may opt out of some tracking cookies that will be able to identify you on third-party ad networks we feature by using the following links:
http://www.quantcast.com/docs/display/legal/Opt-out+of+Quantcast+Delivery
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
HOW DO YOU COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE?
Pursuant to the provisions of the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect personal identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age without the consent of a parent or legal guardian. Thus, when a guest under 13 years of age registers, he/she is required to provide the email address of his/her parent (or legal guardian). We then contact the parent (or legal guardian) and alert them to the child's registration. We require the parent or guardian to validate the account in order for the potential member to become a registered member. However, even after an account has been validated, no personally identifiable information collected from guests under the age of thirteen will ever be sold or provided to any third parties, or used for any marketing or promotional purposes. In addition, parents may request to review the personally identifiable information collected from their child, may ask to have that information deleted, and may refuse to allow further collection or use of their child's personally identifiable information at any time. To request such review or to give instructions regarding the personally identifiable information we have collected about a child, parents/legal guardians should contact us in one of the ways mentioned above in the section entitled "How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?" or in the section below entitled "Questions? Contact Us."
THIRD PARTY LINKS, CO-BRAND RELATIONSHIPS, AND PUBLIC FORUMS
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, Roto Sports, Inc. may choose various third party web sites to link to, link from, and frame within, the Roto Sports, Inc. Network. Roto Sports, Inc. also participates in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to its users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with Roto Sports, Inc., we have no control over these linked sites, each of which have separate privacy and data collection practices independent of Roto Sports, Inc.. We have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. Please make sure you are comfortable with the privacy practices of every site you visit before providing the site with your personal information. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk.
We also make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to you on the Roto Sports, Inc. Network. Please remember that we cannot control the information that is shared by members and that anything you voluntarily provide in any public area of the Internet will be publicly available to other visitors on that web site and potentially to other third parties. Thus, please note that you should always exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose any of your personal information in these and similar areas.
CALIFORNIA-SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you are a California resident, state law requires us to provide you with some additional information regarding how we collect, use, and share your “personally identifiable information” (as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)).
Categories of personal information we collect
Throughout this Privacy Policy, we discuss in detail the specific pieces of personal information we collect from and about users. Under the CCPA, we are also required to provide you with the “categories” of personal information we collect. The categories we may collect are: identifiers (such as name and email address); commercial information (such as subscription data or league information); internet or other network or device activity (such as services usage); geolocation information (e.g., your city and state based on IP address); inference data about you; and other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with you.
How we use and disclose these categories of personal information
We use and disclose the categories of personal information we collect from and about you consistent with the various business purposes we discuss throughout this Policy, and how you engage with the Service. Please see the relevant section(s) above for more information.
If you are a resident of the state of California, the CCPA allows you to make certain requests regarding your personal information. Specifically, the CCPA allows you to request:
Information about the categories of personal information we collect or disclose about you; the categories of sources of such information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information; and the categories of third parties with whom we share/disclose personal information. Such information is also set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Provide access to and/or a copy of certain information we hold about you.
Delete certain stored information we have about you.
Provide you with information about the financial incentives or discounts that we offer to you, if any.
The CCPA further provides you with the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising any of the rights outlined in this section.
We will consider all requests and provide our response within the time period stated by applicable law. Please note, however, that certain information may be exempt from such requests in some circumstances, which may include if we need to keep processing your information or to comply with a legal obligation. We will let you know where this is the case or if certain rights don’t apply in your country or state of residence. We also will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before responding to a request, which might include, at a minimum, depending on the sensitivity of the information you are requesting and the type of request you are making, verifying your name and email address. You are also permitted to designate an authorized agent to submit certain requests on your behalf. In order for an authorized agent to be verified, you must provide the authorized agent with signed, written permission to make such request or a power of attorney. We may also follow up with you to verify your identity before processing the authorized agent’s request.
Additionally, exercising your deletion right may mean that you may no longer be able to use the Service.
If you would like further information regarding your legal rights under California law or would like to exercise any of them, please contact us at support@rotowire.com.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer personally identifiable information to outside parties.
Right to Data Removal
You can request your information be removed from our systems at any time.
You can have your data removed from our systems at any time by requesting an account deletion. This will remove your name, email address, and any other information stored in our systems. However, for legal and reporting purposes, your transaction history will be saved but will not be associated with you in any way.
Additionally, we can provide you with a list containing your personal information that we store in our systems.
To have your information removed from our systems, or to request your information sent to you, please send us an e-mail at support@rotowire.com.
YOUR CONSENT
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Roto Sports, Inc. as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what limited circumstances we disclose it. This policy was last updated January 1, 2020. Continued access or use of the web site shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this privacy statement.
QUESTIONS? CONTACT US
If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with our site, please do not hesitate to contact:
Customer Service: support@rotowire.com
TERMS AND CONDITIONS
This service is provided on an "as-is" basis. Although RotoWire applies its best efforts to maintain this service, no warranty is offered and no fitness for any particular purpose is guaranteed. By signing up for this service you agree that Roto Sports, Inc. is not liable for any defects, lost profits, or any damages that may result from defects of any kind. You further agree that you are the owner of the e-mail address which you are registering, or that you have the express permission of the owner to register that address with this service. You agree that as a sponsored service, messages sent to the above e-mail address by this service may contain advertisements. RotoWire agrees not to knowingly divulge your e-mail address to third parties, and further that your e-mail address submitted here will be used only to provide and improve upon this service. You agree that RotoWire is not liable for the acquisition of your address by third parties without RotoWire's knowledge. RotoWire agrees to take reasonable measures to protect your address and any other personal information.
×
Fantasy Sports
Contact UsLogin
Fantasy Sports
HomeNFLMLBNBASoccerNHLGolfCollege FBWNBAEuroLeagueMMANASCARCollege BBEsportsKBOAFLNPBTennisCricketCFLCPBL
Daily Fantasy (DFS)
HomeNFLMLBNBASoccerNHLGolfCollege FBWNBAEuroLeagueMMANASCARCollege BBEsportsKBOAFLNPBTennisCricketCFLDream11
Sports Betting
HomeNFLMLBNBANHLMMACollege FBCollege BBSoccerGolfWNBANASCARKBOAFLEuroLeague
